import { TopicData } from '../../types/types';

const alphabetData: TopicData[] = [
  {
    front: 'A',
    back: 'A is for apple 🍎',
  },
  {
    front: 'B',
    back: 'B is for bear 🧸',
  },
  {
    front: 'C',
    back: 'C is for cat 🐱',
  },
  {
    front: 'D',
    back: 'D is for dog 🐶',
  },
  {
    front: 'E',
    back: 'E is for egg 🥚',
  },
  {
    front: 'F',
    back: 'F is for frog 🐸',
  },
  {
    front: 'G',
    back: 'G is for giraffe 🦒',
  },
  {
    front: 'H',
    back: 'H is for hand 👋',
  },
  {
    front: 'I',
    back: 'I is for ice 🧊',
  },
  {
    front: 'J',
    back: 'J is for joker 🃏',
  },
  {
    front: 'K',
    back: 'K is for king 👑',
  },
  {
    front: 'L',
    back: 'L is for love ❤️',
  },
  {
    front: 'M',
    back: 'M is for money 💰',
  },
  {
    front: 'N',
    back: 'N is for nose 🤥',
  },
  {
    front: 'O',
    back: 'O is for orange 🍊',
  },
  {
    front: 'P',
    back: 'P is for pink 🌸',
  },
  {
    front: 'Q',
    back: 'Q is for queen 👸',
  },
  {
    front: 'R',
    back: 'R is for rose 🌹',
  },
  {
    front: 'S',
    back: 'S is for sand 🏝',
  },
  {
    front: 'T',
    back: 'T is for tea 🫖',
  },
  {
    front: 'U',
    back: 'U is for umbrella ☔️',
  },
  {
    front: 'V',
    back: 'V is for van 🚚 ',
  },
  {
    front: 'W',
    back: 'W is for wet 💦',
  },
  {
    front: 'X',
    back: 'X is for xmas 🎄',
  },
  {
    front: 'Y',
    back: 'Y is for yes 👍',
  },
  {
    front: 'Z',
    back: 'Z is for zebra 🦓',
  },
];

export { alphabetData };
